data = [
    {
      "question": "What or who is 'Dracula vampira'?",
      "answerA": "person",
      "answerB": "plant",
      "answerC": "animal",
      "answerD": "club",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many people live in France (2017)",
      "answerA": "43 mio",
      "answerB": "110 mio",
      "answerC": "67 mio",
      "answerD": "",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the capital of Azerbaijan?",
      "answerA": "Baku",
      "answerB": "Baka",
      "answerC": "",
      "answerD": "",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "This quiz is...",
      "answerA": "awesome ;)",
      "answerB": "",
      "answerC": "",
      "answerD": "",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Database normalization is the process...",
      "answerA": " of putting some normal people into a database who can keep things from getting weird.",
      "answerB": " restructuring a relational database in accordance with a series of so-called normal forms in order to reduce data redundancy and improve data integrity.",
      "answerC": " of trying to improve the read performance of a database, at the expense of losing some write performance, by adding redundant copies of data or by grouping data.",
      "answerD": " restructuring a non-relational database in accordance with a series of so-called normal forms in order to reduce data redundancy and improve data integrity.",
      "correct": " answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "From which language is the word ‘ketchup’ derived?",
      "answerA": "French",
      "answerB": "Malay",
      "answerC": "English",
      "answerD": "Hindi",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "Brie and Camembert are types of which food?",
      "answerA": "Bread",
      "answerB": "Wine",
      "answerC": "Cheese",
      "answerD": "Meat",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the popular video game series, what type of animal is Sonic?",
      "answerA": "Dog",
      "answerB": "Cat",
      "answerC": "Hedgehog",
      "answerD": "Mouse",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "H2O is the chemical compound for...?",
      "answerA": "Water",
      "answerB": "Gold",
      "answerC": "Uranium",
      "answerD": "Oxygen",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the ‘MI’ in ‘MI6’ stand for?",
      "answerA": "Massive Intellect",
      "answerB": "Mighty Inc.",
      "answerC": "Military Intelligence",
      "answerD": "Manchester Inc.",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which religion is Krishna a god?",
      "answerA": "Judaism",
      "answerB": "Christianity",
      "answerC": "Hinduism",
      "answerD": "Buddhism",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Tolkien's Middle Earth, What Sindarin word was Aragorn known by when he was a child?",
      "answerA": "Estel - meaning 'hope' or 'trust'",
      "answerB": "Amdir - meaning 'looking up'",
      "answerC": "Aeluin - meaning 'blue lake'",
      "answerD": "Míriel - meaning 'sparkling like jewels'",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Tolkien's Middle Earth, What do the Elves call the Hobbits?",
      "answerA": "The Mellon",
      "answerB": "The Periannath",
      "answerC": "The Onodrim",
      "answerD": "The Urulóki",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct conversion from inches to meters?".
      "answerA": "1 inch = 0.003 meters",
      "answerB": "1 inch = 0.03 meters",
      "answerC": "1 inch = 0.3 meters",  
      "answerD": "1 inch = 3 meters",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the abbreviation OLED stand for?".
      "answerA": "Odd-Voltage Light Emiting Diode",
      "answerB": "Ordered Light Emiting Diode",
      "answerC": "Osfactoric Light Emiting Diode",  
      "answerD": "Organic Light Emiting Diode",
      "correct": "answerD"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was Google's originally called?",
      "answerA": "Googol",
      "answerB": "Backrub",
      "answerC": "Alphabet",
      "answerD": "Google",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the most pirated Software?,
      "answerA": "Adobe Photoshop",
      "answerB": "Winzip",
      "answerC": "MSOffice",
      "answerD": "Steam",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which airport has IATA code of BHD?",
      "answerA": "Baghdad International Airport",
      "answerB": "George Best Belfast City Airport",
      "answerC": "Berlin Brandenburg Airport",
      "answerD": "Hancock County-Bar Harbor Airport",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which century was William Shakespeare born?",
      "answerA": "14th century (1396)",
      "answerB": "15th century (1465)",
      "answerC": "16th century (1564)",
      "answerD": "17th century (1695)",
      "correct": "answerC"
    {
      "question": "What is the percentage of water on Earth?",
      "answerA": "56",
      "answerB": "80",
      "answerC": "71",
      "answerD": "60",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Name of planet after earth ?",
      "answerA": "Mercurius",
      "answerB": "Saturn",
      "answerC": "Mars",
      "answerD": "Jupiter",
      "correct": "Venus"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who built the Taj Mahal?",
      "answerA": "Akbar",
      "answerB": "1Aurangjeb",
      "answerC": "Shah Jahan",
      "answerD": "Jhangir",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who built Fatehpur Sikri?",
      "answerA": "Akbar",
      "answerB": "1Aurangjeb",
      "answerC": "Shah Jahan",
      "answerD": "Jhangir",
      "correct": "answerA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first person to discover the route to India?",
      "answerA": "Columbus",
      "answerB": "Marco Polo",
      "answerC": "Vasco Da gama",
      "answerD": "Julius Ceaser",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the first ruler of the Mauryan Empire?",
      "answerA": "Bimbisar",
      "answerB": "Ashoka",
      "answerC": "Chandragupta Maurya",
      "answerD": "Gopala",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the capital of Indonesia?",
      "answerA": "Bali",
      "answerB": "Bandung",
      "answerC": "Surabaya",
      "answerD": "Jakarta",
      "correct": "Kuala Lumpur"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whose mother complained about his swearing in the film GoodFellas?",
      "answerA": "Ray Liotta",
      "answerB": "Joe Pesci",
      "answerC": "Robert De Niro",
      "answerD": "Paul Sorvino",
      "correct": "answerB"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Kelvin scale measure?",
      "answerA": "Height",
      "answerB": "Toughness",
      "answerC": "Temperature",
      "answerD": "Weight",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many strings does a standard guitar have?",
      "answerA": "2",
      "answerB": "12",
      "answerC": "24",
      "answerD": "6",
      "correct": "answerD"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did Alice enter Wonderland?",
      "answerA": "Large Door",
      "answerB": "Tiny Door",
      "answerC": "Rabbithole",
      "answerD": "Window",
      "correct": "answerC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the final act at Woodstock?",
      "answerA": "Jimi Hendrix",
      "answerB": "Janis Joplin",
      "answerC": "The Who",
      "answerD": "Joe Cocker",
      "correct": "answerA"
    }
  ];
